<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome on ACM Special Interest Group on Software Engineering (SIGSOFT)</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome on ACM Special Interest Group on Software Engineering (SIGSOFT)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://acmsigsoft.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SIGSOFT Blog</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/ACM-SIGSOFT-Blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/ACM-SIGSOFT-Blog/</guid><description>We are excited to launch this blog, as a way to enhance the communication between the SIGSOFT EC and the software engineering community, create a sense of community within SIGSOFT, and publicise software engineering and SIGSOFT activities to the outside world.
Blog Home Page</description></item><item><title> ACM SIGSOFT - SIGBED Frank Anger Award</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/anger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/anger/</guid><description>In honor of our late colleague and friend, Dr. Frank Anger, the ACM Special Interest Group on Software Engineering has joined together with the ACM Special Interest Group on Embedded Systems to present the Frank Anger Memorial Award. Dr. Frank Anger, an outstanding national leader in the field of software engineering, died in a tragic automobile accident on July 8, 2004. One of Frank&amp;rsquo;s primary goals was supporting the crossover of ideas between research communities engaged in software.</description></item><item><title> CARES Purpose and Annual Reporting</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/SIGSOFT-CARES/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/SIGSOFT-CARES/</guid><description>Purpose # CARES is a subcommittee of ACM SIGSOFT. All ACM SIG events and communications abide by ACM’s policy against discrimination and harassment. All ACM SIG publications abide by ACM’s policies on plagiarism, misrepresentation, and falsification; on coercion and abuse in the ACM publications process; and on roles and responsibilities in ACM publishing. If a violation of any of these policies occur, ACM urges reporting the incident to the event chair or to ACM leadership, as indicated on those webpages.</description></item><item><title> Distinguished Service Award</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/distinguishedService/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/distinguishedService/</guid><description>This annual award is presented to individuals who have contributed dedicated and important service to the software engineering community. The award typically goes to a single person but can also be assigned to multiple people for joint contributions.
Recipients receive a plaque engraved with their name and signed by the chair of SIGSOFT and share a $1000 honorarium. The award is presented by the SIGSOFT chair at ICSE during ICSE&amp;rsquo;s award presentation session.</description></item><item><title> Early Career Researcher Award</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/earlyCareerResearcher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/earlyCareerResearcher/</guid><description>This award is presented to an individual or individuals who have made outstanding contributions in the area of software engineering as an early career investigator.
To be eligible for nomination for the award, individuals&amp;rsquo; most recent computer-related educational degree (baccalaureate, masters, or doctoral degree) must have been awarded no more than seven years prior to the date of nomination. The 7-year window may be extended for extenuating circumstances such as parental or medical leave.</description></item><item><title> Outstanding Doctoral Dissertation Award</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/dissertation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/dissertation/</guid><description>The SIGSOFT Outstanding Doctoral Dissertation Award is presented annually to the author of an outstanding doctoral dissertation in the area of Software Engineering. The author of the winning dissertation will be invited to publish a dissertation summary in the SIGSOFT newsletter, Software Engineering Notes (SEN). The award includes a $1000 honorarium and a plaque for the author, which is presented at the International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE), and funding support for the recipient to travel to ICSE to receive the award (including a registration to ICSE).</description></item><item><title>CARES Resources</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/RESOURCES/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/RESOURCES/</guid><description>ACM Resources
Policy Against Harassment at ACM Activities, by the ACM ACM Harassment and Discrimination Reporting Procedures, by the ACM Form for reporting violations of ACM code of conduct, by the ACM Addressing Harassment at ACM Events: Volunteer Training, by the ACM Information on inclusion and diversity
The diversity and inclusion revolution: Eight powerful truths, by Juliet Bourke Valuing Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in Our Computing Community, by Timothy Pinkston Information about implicit bias</description></item><item><title>SIGSOFT CAPS</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/CAPS/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/CAPS/</guid><description>SIGSOFT Travel Support and Childcare Assistance at Conferences - CAPS # CAPS provides support for students and professionals to attend the conferences and events sponsored by ACM SIGSOFT. Currently, CAPS applications are open for:
ASE 2022: CAPS application deadline: September 5, 2022. To apply: fill your application at this link
MODELS 2022: CAPS application deadline: September 9, 2022. To apply: fill your application at this link
ESEC/FSE 2022: CAPS application deadline: September 12, 2022.</description></item><item><title>CARES Bylaws</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/BYLAWS/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/BYLAWS/</guid><description>CARES mission statement The CARES committee was established to encourage a welcoming harassment-free research community at professional meetings sponsored by SIGSOFT. By its existence, it seeks to discourage bad behavior and offer a friendly ear for community members to discuss their experiences confidentially.
CARES governance policies The remainder of this document outlines the policies for governance of the CARES committee, including chair rotation, membership, autonomy, and conflicts of interest on the CARES committee.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Contact/</guid><description>Chair: Thomas Zimmermann # Microsoft Research One Microsoft Way Redmond, WA 98004 Phone: +1-425-703-8450 chair_SIGSOFT@acm.org Vice Chair: Marsha Chechik # University of Toronto chechik@cs.toronto.edu ACM Program Director for SIGSOFT: James Peeples # ACM Headquarters 1601 Broadway, 10th Floor New York, New York 10019-7434 USA Tel: +1-212-626-0603 Fax: +1-212-302-5826 peeples@hq.acm.org Social Media Chair: Sridhar Chimalakonda # Department of Computer Science and Engineering Indian Institute of Technology Tirupati, India http://researchweb.iitt.ac.in/~sridhar_ch ch@iittp.ac.in Refer to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Adding SIGSOFT CARES</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Adding CARES to the SIGSOFT Website # Adding CARES to the SIGSOFT Website</description></item><item><title/><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/impactPaper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/impactPaper/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/influencialEducator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/Awards/influencialEducator/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>