<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ACM Special Interest Group on Software Engineering</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/</link><description>Recent content on ACM Special Interest Group on Software Engineering</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Purpose and Annual Reporting</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/SIGSOFT-CARES/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/SIGSOFT-CARES/</guid><description>Purpose # CARES is a subcommittee of ACM SIGSOFT. All ACM SIG events and communications abide by ACM’s policy against discrimination and harassment. All ACM SIG publications abide by ACM’s policies on plagiarism, misrepresentation, and falsification; on coercion and abuse in the ACM publications process; and on roles and responsibilities in ACM publishing. If a violation of any of these policies occur, ACM urges reporting the incident to the event chair or to ACM leadership, as indicated on those webpages.</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/RESOURCES/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/RESOURCES/</guid><description>ACM Resources
Policy Against Harassment at ACM Activities, by the ACM ACM Harassment and Discrimination Reporting Procedures, by the ACM Form for reporting violations of ACM code of conduct, by the ACM Addressing Harassment at ACM Events: Volunteer Training, by the ACM Information on inclusion and diversity
The diversity and inclusion revolution: Eight powerful truths, by Juliet Bourke Valuing Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in Our Computing Community, by Timothy Pinkston Information about implicit bias</description></item><item><title>SIGSOFT CARES Bylaws</title><link>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/BYLAWS/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acmsigsoft.github.io/docs/Website/SIGSOFT-CARES/BYLAWS/</guid><description>CARES mission statement The CARES committee was established to encourage a welcoming harassment-free research community at professional meetings sponsored by SIGSOFT. By its existence, it seeks to discourage bad behavior and offer a friendly ear for community members to discuss their experiences confidentially.
CARES governance policies The remainder of this document outlines the policies for governance of the CARES committee, including chair rotation, membership, autonomy, and conflicts of interest on the CARES committee.</description></item></channel></rss>